<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
   <name>Terminators</name>
   <author>Crackajack, Thumbstick</author>
   <packageId>Crackajack.Terminators</packageId>
   <supportedVersions>
	  <li>1.5</li>
   </supportedVersions>
   
   <description>CrackaJack and Thumbstick proudly present: 
   Terminators. 
   This is a loveletter to the old killing machine.
   With this mod we introduce the iconic T800 and T880 terminator models and two style fitting weapons .
   As a pretty unique feature both change appearance to reflect their state of damage and also have custom wounds, as shown in the pictures. 
   In other words they visibly lose chunks of flesh exposing inner machinery- i had a lot of fun drawing this, hehe. 
   Terminator raids and help events can be disabled and configured.
   Skynet CPU cores are rare quest rewards, needed for gestation.
   
   -The fearsome model T800 is a "mechanoid", requiring a mechanitor. 
   Capable of most work and with an ability to equip any weapon like a human can. Due to their advanced autonomous ai they dont require any bandwidth to control.
   Slow but sturdy, fine marksmen.
   All of them are jacked and wear sunglasses and a leather coat. The perfect disguised mechanical bodyguard, if you can get one, or major threat to your well beeing.
   
   -T880 are "human", its a unique xenotype. 
   They are slow in movement and reaction, but as tough as you´d expect and require nothing but nuclear fuel cells on a rare but regular basis. 
   craft these from uranium at the machining table.
   T880 are stone cold killers that can´t feel pain and will only be stopped by major structure damage.
   Some rare cases have infiltrated or joined other cultures, claiming to have decided against following skynet directives.
   
   -Skynet5A2 rifle: An expensive and futuristic machine gun, spitting a lot of lead.
   
   -Colt1911: Custom longslide version with a laser on top, like in the first movie.
   
   Credits: 
   Thumbstick, C# programming;
   CrackaJack, art and XML.
   Special thanks: VE crew for their framework. Arnold for beeing big. aRandomKiwi for ATTX, we relight the torch, man.</description>
   <modDependencies>
	<li>
		<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
		<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
		<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
	</li>	
	<li>
		<packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</packageId>
		<displayName>Biotech</displayName>
	</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
			<displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
	<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
	<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
	<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
	<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
  </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>